Nee-sama!
So cramped.
I get it now.
Step 1, restrain me in a coffin.
Step 2, bury me under a gravestone.
Step 3, start a three count.
And that's as far as this domain's
guaranteed-hit effect applies.
It is a special-grade disease curse.
If I don't break out of the coffin
before the count is up,
I'll contract that disease and die.
The real issue is that gravestone.
If I eat that attack twice more,
I'll no longer be able to move, as well.
I wouldn't want to fight
Geto-kun in that state.
Ui Ui, are you all right?
Yes, Nee-sama.
It's probably reflexively
targeting the person with
the strongest cursed energy in its domain.
Only two crows were sucked
into the domain with me.
I was right.
So in order to take it down,
I'll have to shift its target to Ui Ui
so he can buy me time to operate freely.
But Ui Ui will die after taking
one hit from that gravestone.
Ui Ui...
Will you die for me?
Are you sure that's all right? May I die for you?
The moment I released my cursed energy,
Nee-sama suppressed hers.
I understand everything now,
Nee-sama!
Did you think I only brought
that boy to carry my things?
Nee-sama's request that I risk my life
is the signal permitting me
to use my cursed energy.
New Shadow Style: Simple Domain
Ui Ui's role is dealing with domains.
It goes against my principles
to owe anyone anything.
So I leave that aspect up to him.
What do you think is the greatest way
to instantly boost a sorcerer's base power?
It's using a pact that
puts your life on the line!
Right, Nee-sama?!
Yes!
The crowning attack of Nee-sama's cursed
technique, Black Bird Manipulation,
is Kamikaze: Bird Strike!
She forces her crow to commit
suicide, which in return
removes the limit on a crow's
normally feeble cursed energy,
as she makes them slam into her opponent.
No human is able to stop her Bird Strike,
with the sole exception of Satoru Gojo.
Okay, everyone, it's the main event.
Will you die for me?
Not bad.
For a modern sorcerer.
Episode 38
Fluctuations
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Shibuya Incident
Satoru Gojo has been sealed, huh?
I feel like I've been bushwhacked.
Me, too.
Geto-san is involved, though,
even if he is a fake.
I imagine the trick lies there.
I'd be happy to toast
the fall of the Gojo clan.
Go home if you're not going to help!
Go home, huh?
That's what you should be doing, Maki.
Right, grade 1 sorcerer, Nanami-dono?
Maki-san,
you should do what he says in this regard.
I'll be far more useful than some drunkard.
22:20  Shibuya Station, Inokashira Line
Avenue Exit
Have you been drinking?
No, I hafn'h been dwinking.
I guess there's never been a case
where I was better off alone.
Nanami-san.
Yes.
I'll take this one.
You guys are a bit too slow.
Did you see that?
No.
It must be his technique.
How many people have you eaten?
Jogo...
Mahito...
Hanami...
Hanami!
How dare...
How dare you kill Hanami?!
...kill Hanami?!
I see. No wonder you were weak.
You were still only a Curse Womb, then.
Water?!
And such a vast amount of it!
Cursed spirit,
do you know how many frames there
are in one second of animation?
It's not "cursed spirit." I am Dagon.
There's a modern tendency to
raise resolutions and frame rates.
There's Hanami, Jogo, and Mahito, too.
Upscaling to 4K, and 60fps
frame interpolation...
We all...
They don't cause anyone any trouble
when done for personal use, so that's fine.
However, modern TVs have their damn
frame interpolation set to "on" by default!
It's not like "unwanted favor"
has become a dead phrase already!
Nothing is more lamentable than that!
Creating that soap opera effect...
We all have names!
Don't you agree that's uncultured?!
Whoa there.
No damage.
Or rather, it feels more
like he has endless HP.
I can't believe two grade 1s like
us couldn't exorcise it together.
What dire straits.
Shit!
If the old man hadn't used his technique,
I would have died there.
I'm ashamed.
A defensive barrier of water, huh?
Can you produce large-scale attacks
at the same time, too?
You have too much cursed energy.
You still have several
techniques left, right?
So what should I do?
That's easy.
I'll kill you quickly,
before you can use your technique!
Impossible!
Of course, you can hover, too, right?
I'd escape upward, too.
I can't activate my technique!
It's this man!
It's this man's fault!
He's fast!
Probably faster than Jogo!
Projection Sorcery.
The cursed technique of Naobito Zen'in.
It splits one second into 24
frames from his field of view,
and allows him to trace the actions
created in those frames at the start.
While the technique is active,
anyone Naobito touches
with his hand must also
define their actions
within 1/24th of a second.
If they fail to do so,
then their action hangs,
and they remain frozen for one second.
There are risks.
The actions defined cannot
be edited halfway through.
Creating actions that excessively
ignore physics and paths of motion
will result in him freezing, as well.
Still, with his innate sense
for frame beats and time,
he's managed to become the fastest
sorcerer, aside from Satoru Gojo.
I won't let you.
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Domain Expansion:
Horizon of the Captivating Skandha.
Shikigami?! So this is the domain's
guaranteed-hit attack?
I didn't notice them until they struck.
No, they didn't even exist until they hit.
Secret Art: Falling Blossom Emotion.
An anti-domain technique passed
down among the big three clans.
Like Simple Domain, the user does
not activate their own domain,
and instead, the moment the domain's
guaranteed-hit attack activates,
it protects the user by countering
with their own cursed energy.
I knew that man was
different from the others.
I'm done testing their strength.
I'll split my power, 70% to the mustached man,
and 30% to the man in a suit.
Activate technique: Death Swarm!
Maki-san!
The shikigami aren't
heading straight for us!
They'll be gouging out our
flesh in the next instant!
Don't think about it!
The moment you feel contact,
cut them down one after another!
That's the best you can manage
with your scant cursed en—
Nanami-san!
The surge of shikigami isn't abating at all.
Is it possible the technique
embedded into this domain is—
Falling—
The sea is the source of all life.
Weak.
You're first.
Death Swarm is a swarm of
endlessly emerging shikigami.
If you're gonna call me weak,
then kill me in a single blow,
Octobitch.
Then I'll devour you...
Shit!
...just like the other two.
Maki-san!
Megumi!
You really are...
one hell of a cheeky underclassman!
It's him!
That octopus!
He's the source of this domain!
You dare infiltrate my domain on your own?
How foolish.
What?!
The guaranteed-hit effect
of my domain is gone!
That boy is deploying his domain.
Right now, his domain and
mine are playing tug-of-war.
In order to regain my guaranteed-hit effect,
I'll have to crush his domain first.
Easily done!
The other two?
Ino-san tapped out.
Itadori's acting on his own.
I'll protect you.
Please focus on your domain.
That man...
He endured Death Swarm for roughly a minute?
The mustachioed man, too!
You only took one measly right arm.
But it had 71 years in it.
That's going to cost you!
If this state keeps up, we have a chance.
If it keeps up.
Nanami-san!
That octopus currently thinks our
domains are pushing for control.
But my goal is different.
I'll open a small hole
in the barrier of this domain!
The hole I entered through
is already sealed.
It's harder to open one
from inside than outside,
but I can open a hole large enough for
someone to pass through for a few seconds.
That thing isn't Gojo-sensei.
It shouldn't be able to use Domain
Expansion multiple times in one day.
Once we're all out of
this domain, we can win.
The edge of his domain is beneath my feet.
I can tell, since I touched it when I entered.
I'm ready to go at any time!
If all three of you jump in once...
None of this leaving yourself
behind alone, all right?
I'm risking my life,
but I don't intend to throw it away.
You two!
Gather 'round!
They're bolstering their defense of the boy?
That just groups them up for me to—
No!
He figured it out?! But it's too late!
To Fushiguro-kun's feet!
Don't you think sibling relationships tend
to show through in a person's character?
Nee-sama, that could encourage
the discriminatory
idea that all only children are selfish!
You're right, that's not good!
Are you refuting Nee-sama?
Huh?!
Next Episode
Fluctuations, Part 2
Next time, "Fluctuations, Part 2."
What about Satoru Gojo?
He's an only child, of course.